
const l_list = [
        
    {title: 'Hanna and John',
    p1: 'Прослушайте текст на английском и выполните задания',
    test: [
        {num: 1,
        question: 'How is Hanna behaving?',
        ans1: '...',
        ans2: 'Good',
        ans3: 'Fine',
        ans4: 'Bad',
        right: '4'},
        {num: 2,
        question: 'How is John behaving?',
        ans1: '...',
        ans2: 'Fine',
        ans3: 'Bad',
        ans4: 'Good',
        right: '2'},
        {num: 3,
        question: 'What happened at Hanna?',
        ans1: '...',
        ans2: 'Sne has many jobs',
        ans3: 'Sne has much homework and headache',
        ans4: 'Her cat is died',
        right: '3'},
        {num: 4,
        question: 'Does John want to help Hanna?',
        ans1: '...',
        ans2: 'Yes',
        ans3: 'No',
        ans4: 'May be',
        right: '2'},
        {num: 5,
        question: 'How many pills does Hanna need?',
        ans1: '...',
        ans2: 'One',
        ans3: 'Five',
        ans4: 'Two',
        right: '4'},
    ],},
    
    {title: 'One little girl',
    p1: 'Прослушайте текст на английском и выполните задания',
    test: [
        {num: 1,
        question: 'What is this story about?',
        ans1: '...',
        ans2: 'On the love of the girl',
        ans3: 'Relationship of the boy and the girl',
        ans4: 'About the father of the boy',
        right: '3'},
        {num: 2,
        question: 'Was the girl`s family poor?',
        ans1: '...',
        ans2: 'Yes',
        ans3: 'No',
        ans4: 'Not stated',
        right: '3'},
        {num: 3,
        question: 'The boy`s family was rich. Is it true or false?',
        ans1: '...',
        ans2: 'False',
        ans3: 'Not stated',
        ans4: 'True',
        right: '2'},
        {num: 4,
        question: 'Why did the girl`s parents not want her to communicate with the boy?',
        ans1: '...',
        ans2: 'He was sick',
        ans3: 'His parent were poor',
        ans4: 'He beat the girl',
        right: '3'},
        {num: 5,
        question: 'Where did the boy and girl play?',
        ans1: '...',
        ans2: 'in the house',
        ans3: 'in the castle',
        ans4: 'in the garden',
        right: '4'},
    ],},

    {title: 'The bear',
    p1: 'Прослушайте текст на английском и выполните задания',
    test: [
        {num: 1,
        question: 'What did the bear do?',
        ans1: '...',
        ans2: 'Slept',
        ans3: 'Ate',
        ans4: 'Lay',
        right: '2'},
        {num: 2,
        question: 'Who came to the bear?',
        ans1: '...',
        ans2: 'Deer',
        ans3: 'Mouse',
        ans4: 'Fox',
        right: '3'},
        {num: 3,
        question: 'What did the guest want?',
        ans1: '...',
        ans2: 'Talk to the bear',
        ans3: 'Dine',
        ans4: 'Steal the honey',
        right: '4'},
        {num: 4,
        question: 'What did the guest do?',
        ans1: '...',
        ans2: 'Took honey',
        ans3: 'Had lunch',
        ans4: 'Sat down',
        right: '2'},
        {num: 5,
        question: 'Did the bear wake up?',
        ans1: '...',
        ans2: 'No',
        ans3: 'Not stated',
        ans4: 'Yes',
        right: '2'},
    ],},
    
    
    
]

export {l_list}